第一节：听小对话，回答问题。
Wow! That's a great photo!
Did you take it?
No, my sister did.
She took it for the school newspaper.
Excuse me, Carrie.
Are you from London or New York?
Neither. I'm from Australia, but my grandparents are English.
Good morning, Betty.
You look so weak.
What happened? Nothing.
I just stayed up late last night.
We'll have a math test today, you know.
You look good in this suit, Cathy.
How does your job interview go today?
I'm hopeful this time.
I've finished my second interview with this school.
Everything okay with your meal?
Delicious. Thank you.
Yes, great. Can we take the bill?
Of course. Yes, James.
听下面一段对话，回答第六七小题。
Our class is flying to Paris for our school trip.
Great. How exciting.
When do you leave home?
Tomorrow morning at 5 a.m.
Oh no, at 4 a.m.
Really? That's crazy.
How will you wake up that early?
I don't know.
I hope Mom will wake me up.
Hey, why not join us?
Good idea. It'll be fun.
Count me in.
Hello, Helen. Look at your smile on your face.
Any good news?
Yes, James. Our class is flying to Paris for our school trip.
Great. How exciting.
When do you leave home?
Tomorrow morning at 5 a.m.
Oh no, at 4 a.m.
Really? That's crazy.
How will you wake up that early?
I don't know.
I hope Mom will wake me up.
Hey, why not join us?
Good idea. It'll be fun.
Count me in.
听下面一段对话，回答第八至十小题。
Good morning and welcome to Radio Kent.
This morning we're talking about volunteer work.
On our phone line, we have Mike from Canterbury.
Right now he and his friend Jim are in Africa.
Morning, Mike. Hi.
Carol. What do you do there in Africa?
I work as a volunteer in a medical school.
I teach English and medicine here.
And what are you doing right now?
I'm having breakfast.
Do you cook breakfast yourself?
No. Jim does it every day.
And lunch and dinner too.
We do all our own housework.
Really? And tell us, do you like being there in Africa?
Oh yes, I love it.
I'm having a great time.
I'm working with wonderful people and I'm learning a lot.
That's great, Mike.
Thanks for your time.
It's my pleasure.
Thanks. Have a good day.
Good morning and welcome to Radio Kent.
This morning we're talking about volunteer work.
On our phone line, we have Mike from Canterbury.
Right now he and his friend Jim are in Africa.
Morning, Mike. Hi.
Carol. What do you do there in Africa?
I work as a volunteer in a medical school.
teach English and medicine here.
And what are you doing right now?
I'm having breakfast.
Do you cook breakfast yourself?
No. Jim does it every day.
And lunch and dinner too.
We do all our own housework.
Really? And tell us, do you like being there in Africa?
Oh yes, I love it.
I'm having a great time.
I'm working with wonderful people and I'm learning a lot.
That's great, Mike.
Thanks for your time.
It's my pleasure.
第三节听独白，回答问题。
Good afternoon, and gentlemen.
Welcome to this fantastic tour of London.
My name's Greg and I'm your guide.
As you can see, we're on an open top bus, so you can see all the places of interest
from your seat and you don't need to walk anywhere.
And please don't worry about the rain.
I'm sure it'll stop soon.
Well, the tour takes two hours and we'll probably finish our tour at five o
Right, okay, so where are we going on our wonderful tour?
First, we'll drive along the most famous shoppy, Ing Street in the world, Oxford
Street. After that, we'll see the famous clock Big Ben.
As we drive along the river, you'll see the London Eye, from which you can see the
whole city on a sunny day.
Then we'll see Tower Bridge and the famous Tower of London before arriving at
Buckingham Palace.
There's a lovely cafe near the palace where you can get a cup of coffee for free.
Okay, now any questions?
Good afternoon, ladies and gentlemen, welcome to this fantastic tour of London.
My name's Greg and I'm your guide.
As you can see, we're on an open top bus, so you can see all the places of interest
from your seat and you don't need to walk anywhere.
And please don't worry about the rain.
I'm sure it'll stop soon.
Well, the tour takes two hours and we'll probably finish our tour at five o
Right, okay, so where are we going on our wonderful tour?
First, we'll drive along the most famous shoppy, Ing Street in the world, Oxford
Street. After that, we'll see the famous clock Big Ben.
As we drive along the river, you'll see the London Eye, from which you can see the
whole city on a sunny day.
Then we'll see Tower Bridge and the famous Tower of London before arriving at
Buckingham Palace.
There's a lovely cafe near the palace
题力测试结束，请关注锦鲤英语微信公众号